<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Pepper&#39;s Pawprint</title>
    <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Pepper&#39;s Pawprint</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 08:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Moro carrot soup for diarrhea</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/moro-carrot-soup-for-diarrhea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/moro-carrot-soup-for-diarrhea/</guid>
      <description>Effect The secret of the carrot soup is the long cooking time, during which an important molecule is released. This has even been scientifically researched.
Due to the long cooking process, important sugar molecules are released from the carrots. The bacteria attach to the sugar molecules, because they are very similar to the intestinal receptors, and so the bacteria are excreted with the feces. Because important mineral salts are lost through the diarrhea, the salt in the carrot soup helps replenish the body&#39;s electrolyte balance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When your dog is &#39;suddenly&#39; old</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/when-your-dog-is-suddenly-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/when-your-dog-is-suddenly-old/</guid>
      <description>Such a process is slow, of course, but it makes me realize that our common path is not endless. Sometimes after getting up, Pepper staggers a bit and has to find his balance in the hip. That&#39;s part of it, especially since his hip isn&#39;t his strongest side.
We are taking day by day and adjust our daily walks according to how he feels. If I see that he is stiff, I am going for shorter walks and we relax more at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rest and exercise diary</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/rest-and-exercise-diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/rest-and-exercise-diary/</guid>
      <description>A rest and exercise diary provides insight into how long your dog sleeps during the day and how often your dog exercises. To make it meaningful, you should answer the following questions.
Ask for walks  When did you walk your dog? (Write down all walks.) How long have you been walking? How long was your dog on a leash and loose / on a long leash? What have you done with your dog along the way (eg searching for threats or other activities)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wild camping</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/wild-camping/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/wild-camping/</guid>
      <description>During the vacation week, we were at the Falun pit and saw the beautiful nature of the 3 national parks: Tresticklan, Fulufjället and Färnebofjärden. We did little hikes almost every day. Since it was very hot at the time of our tour, we were unfortunately unable to take long hikes. Some days we just rested at a lake - Pepper was sleeping and I read a book.
Practical things During wild camping, every place should be left as you found it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chronic Superficial Keratitis</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/chronic-superficial-keratitis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/chronic-superficial-keratitis/</guid>
      <description>At the time, I thought Pepper had a normal eye infection. Both eyes were red in the outer corner. I went to the vet and had his eyes examined. First of all, we received a normal ointment for eye infections. After a week it wasn&#39;t better and we went to the vet again. He re-examined the eye and suspected chronic superficial keratitis.
The chronic superficial keratitis disease can be diagnosed by an eye test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living with a dog: Apartment or house?</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/living-with-a-dog-apartment-or-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/living-with-a-dog-apartment-or-house/</guid>
      <description>Pepper is 11 years old now and we have never lived at the same address for a long time. We have tried many different living situations and I would like to share our experiences with you.
House with enclosed garden When Pepper moved in with us, I was still living at our family home in a house with an enclosed garden. I think a garden is very practical as you can just leave the patio door open in summer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treat boxes</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/treat-boxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/treat-boxes/</guid>
      <description>Take an egg carton or shipping box and fill it with treats. Especially at the beginning it is probably too difficult for your dog to open the closed box. You can just close the box lightly. This makes it easier for your dog.
Once your dog dares to open the box, you can close the box completely in a later attempt. Just look at your dog and increase the difficulty accordingly!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hand puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/hand-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/hand-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>To begin with, take one or multiple treats in your right hand and form a fist. The second hand should be flat besides it. Then the dog is allowed to come and smell on the right hand with the treats. As soon as the dog is touching the left hand with the nose, you can open the first to reward the dog.
Especially in the beginning, the dog probably tries to open the fist with the treats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snuffle mat and searching for treats</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/snuffle-mat-and-searching-for-treats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/snuffle-mat-and-searching-for-treats/</guid>
      <description>The snuffle mat can be used indoors or in the garden. Preferable you have small treats that can be hidden at different places inside the mat. Once you placed all treats, the dog is allowed to search for it.
Maybe your dog is very excited in the beginning. If the snuffle mat is moving a lot, you can hold it so that your dog has it a bit easier. Additionally, it is important to place the treats not to deep inside the mat as it would be too difficult for your dog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rawdiet or Prey Model Raw</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/rawdiet-or-prey-model-raw/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 07:47:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/rawdiet-or-prey-model-raw/</guid>
      <description>How do you feed your dog? What is right and what is wrong?
In the beginning, I just fed what most people feed - dry food. I thought this was good for Pepper and didn&#39;t think any further about it. This went well for a few years, 5 years to be exact. Then the problems started.
In December 2013, Pepper had an eczema on his tail that was a few centimetres long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to do around Ciney, Ardennes</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/things-to-do-around-ciney-ardennes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 07:47:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/things-to-do-around-ciney-ardennes/</guid>
      <description>Domain de Chevetogne The Domaine de Chevetogne is a nature park with different attractions. In the summer months it is possible to swim or play tennis and kids can play on multiple playgrounds all the year.
Additionally, the park has different nature walking routes. Dogs are allowed on a leash and in the winter months you can visited the park for free.
Grotte de Dinant La Merveilleuse The Grotte de Dinant La Merveilleuse is said to be one of the most beautiful caves in Belgium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General tips for Sweden</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/general-tips-for-sweden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 10:46:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/general-tips-for-sweden/</guid>
      <description>It has always been my dream to live in Sweden for a while and this dream came true for my master’s degree. Pepper and I spent a total of 1.5 years in Sweden.
Travel I can only talk about my experiences to travel to Sweden from Germany:
 You can drive through Denmark and then use the Öresund bridge between Copenhagen and Malmö. This bridge connects the two countries. It is easy to buy the tickets online so you don&#39;t have to queue in front of the bridge.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>