<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Health on Pepper&#39;s Pawprint</title>
    <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/category/health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Health on Pepper&#39;s Pawprint</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 08:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/category/health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Moro carrot soup for diarrhea</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/moro-carrot-soup-for-diarrhea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/moro-carrot-soup-for-diarrhea/</guid>
      <description>Effect The secret of the carrot soup is the long cooking time, during which an important molecule is released. This has even been scientifically researched.
Due to the long cooking process, important sugar molecules are released from the carrots. The bacteria attach to the sugar molecules, because they are very similar to the intestinal receptors, and so the bacteria are excreted with the feces. Because important mineral salts are lost through the diarrhea, the salt in the carrot soup helps replenish the body&#39;s electrolyte balance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chronic Superficial Keratitis</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/chronic-superficial-keratitis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/chronic-superficial-keratitis/</guid>
      <description>At the time, I thought Pepper had a normal eye infection. Both eyes were red in the outer corner. I went to the vet and had his eyes examined. First of all, we received a normal ointment for eye infections. After a week it wasn&#39;t better and we went to the vet again. He re-examined the eye and suspected chronic superficial keratitis.
The chronic superficial keratitis disease can be diagnosed by an eye test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rawdiet or Prey Model Raw</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/rawdiet-or-prey-model-raw/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 07:47:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/rawdiet-or-prey-model-raw/</guid>
      <description>How do you feed your dog? What is right and what is wrong?
In the beginning, I just fed what most people feed - dry food. I thought this was good for Pepper and didn&#39;t think any further about it. This went well for a few years, 5 years to be exact. Then the problems started.
In December 2013, Pepper had an eczema on his tail that was a few centimetres long.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>