<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Indoor enrichment on Pepper&#39;s Pawprint</title>
    <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/tag/indoor-enrichment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Indoor enrichment on Pepper&#39;s Pawprint</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 09:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/tag/indoor-enrichment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Treat boxes</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/treat-boxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/treat-boxes/</guid>
      <description>Take an egg carton or shipping box and fill it with treats. Especially at the beginning it is probably too difficult for your dog to open the closed box. You can just close the box lightly. This makes it easier for your dog.
Once your dog dares to open the box, you can close the box completely in a later attempt. Just look at your dog and decrease the difficulty accordingly!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hand puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/hand-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/hand-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>To begin with, take one or multiple treats in your right hand and form a fist. The second hand should be flat besides it. Then the dog is allowed to come and smell on the right hand with the treats. As soon as the dog is touching the left hand with the nose, you can open the first to reward the dog.
Especially in the beginning, the dog probably tries to open the fist with the treats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sniffle mat and searching for treats</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/sniffle-mat-and-searching-for-treats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/sniffle-mat-and-searching-for-treats/</guid>
      <description>The sniffle mat can be used indoors or in the garden. Preferable you have small treats that can be hidden at different places inside the mat. Once you placed all treats, the dog is allowed to search for it.
Maybe your dog is very excited in the beginning. If the sniffle mat is moving a lot, you can hold it so that your dog has it a bit easier. Additionally, it is important to place the treats not to deep inside the mat as it would be too difficult for your dog.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>