<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>General on Pepper&#39;s Pawprint</title>
    <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/category/general/</link>
    <description>Recent content in General on Pepper&#39;s Pawprint</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 08:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/category/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My dog and rewards</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/my-dog-and-rewards/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/my-dog-and-rewards/</guid>
      <description>The most common way is to give your dog some form of food. Instead of a treat, you can also reward your dog by smiling, running or playing together. A reward should always be positive and above all fun! A reward that makes your dog happy will also motivate him and you will remain interesting.
When Pepper was young, I mostly rewarded him with a treat. Nowadays, he gets a smile, sometimes a treat or we just run for a short while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When your dog is &#39;suddenly&#39; old</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/when-your-dog-is-suddenly-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/when-your-dog-is-suddenly-old/</guid>
      <description>Such a process is slow, of course, but it makes me realize that our common path is not endless. Sometimes after getting up, Pepper staggers a bit and has to find his balance in the hip. That&#39;s part of it, especially since his hip isn&#39;t his strongest side.
We are taking day by day and adjust our daily walks according to how he feels. If I see that he is stiff, I am going for shorter walks and we relax more at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rest and exercise diary</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/rest-and-exercise-diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/rest-and-exercise-diary/</guid>
      <description>A rest and exercise diary provides insight into how long your dog sleeps during the day and how often your dog exercises. To make it meaningful, you should answer the following questions.
Ask for walks  When did you walk your dog? (Write down all walks.) How long have you been walking? How long was your dog on a leash and loose / on a long leash? What have you done with your dog along the way (eg searching for threats or other activities)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living with a dog: Apartment or house?</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/living-with-a-dog-apartment-or-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/blog/living-with-a-dog-apartment-or-house/</guid>
      <description>Pepper is 11 years old now and we have never lived at the same address for a long time. We have tried many different living situations and I would like to share our experiences with you.
House with enclosed garden When Pepper moved in with us, I was still living at our family home in a house with an enclosed garden. I think a garden is very practical as you can just leave the patio door open in summer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>