<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Pepper&#39;s Pawprint</title>
    <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Pepper&#39;s Pawprint</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 09:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Treat boxes</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/treat-boxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/treat-boxes/</guid>
      <description>Take an egg carton or shipping box and fill it with treats. Especially at the beginning it is probably too difficult for your dog to open the closed box. You can just close the box lightly. This makes it easier for your dog.
Once your dog dares to open the box, you can close the box completely in a later attempt. Just look at your dog and decrease the difficulty accordingly!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hand puzzle</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/hand-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/hand-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>To begin with, take one or multiple treats in your right hand and form a fist. The second hand should be flat besides it. Then the dog is allowed to come and smell on the right hand with the treats. As soon as the dog is touching the left hand with the nose, you can open the first to reward the dog.
Especially in the beginning, the dog probably tries to open the fist with the treats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sniffle mat and searching for treats</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/sniffle-mat-and-searching-for-treats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/sniffle-mat-and-searching-for-treats/</guid>
      <description>The sniffle mat can be used indoors or in the garden. Preferable you have small treats that can be hidden at different places inside the mat. Once you placed all treats, the dog is allowed to search for it.
Maybe your dog is very excited in the beginning. If the sniffle mat is moving a lot, you can hold it so that your dog has it a bit easier. Additionally, it is important to place the treats not to deep inside the mat as it would be too difficult for your dog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rawdiet or Prey Model Raw</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/rawdiet-or-prey-model-raw/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 07:47:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/rawdiet-or-prey-model-raw/</guid>
      <description>How do you feed your dog? What is right and what is wrong?
In the beginning, I just fed what most people feed - dry food. I thought this was good for Pepper and didn&#39;t think any further about it. This went well for a few years, 5 years to be exact. Then the problems started.
In December 2013, Pepper had an eczema on his tail that was a few centimetres long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to do around Ciney, Ardennes</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/things-to-do-around-ciney-ardennes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 07:47:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/things-to-do-around-ciney-ardennes/</guid>
      <description>Domain de Chevetogne The Domaine de Chevetogne is a nature park with different attractions. In the summer months it is possible to swim or play tennis and kids can play on multiple playgrounds all the year.
Additionally, the park has different nature walking routes. Dogs are allowed on a leash and in the winter months you can visited the park for free.
Grotte de Dinant La Merveilleuse The Grotte de Dinant La Merveilleuse is said to be one of the most beautiful caves in Belgium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General tips for Sweden</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/general-tips-for-sweden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 10:46:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/general-tips-for-sweden/</guid>
      <description>It has always been my dream to live in Sweden for a while and this dream came true for my master’s degree. Pepper and I spent a total of 1.5 years in Sweden.
Travel I can only talk about my experiences to travel to Sweden from Germany:
 You can drive through Denmark and then use the Öresund bridge between Copenhagen and Malmö. This bridge connects the two countries. It is easy to buy the tickets online so you don&#39;t have to queue in front of the bridge.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>