<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Pepper&#39;s Pawprint</title>
    <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Pepper&#39;s Pawprint</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 07:47:39 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rawdiet or Prey Model Raw</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/rawdiet-or-prey-model-raw/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 07:47:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/rawdiet-or-prey-model-raw/</guid>
      <description>How do you feed your dog? What is right and what is wrong?
In the beginning, I just fed what most people feed - dry food. I thought this was good for Pepper and didn&#39;t think any further about it. This went well for a few years, 5 years to be exact. Then the problems started.
In December 2013, Pepper had an eczema on his tail that was a few centimetres long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to do around Ciney, Ardennes</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/things-to-do-around-ciney-ardennes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 07:47:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/things-to-do-around-ciney-ardennes/</guid>
      <description>Domain de Chevetogne The Domaine de Chevetogne is a nature park with different attractions. In the summer months it is possible to swim or play tennis and kids can play on multiple playgrounds all the year.
Additionally, the park has different nature walking routes. Dogs are allowed on a leash and in the winter months you can visited the park for free.
Grotte de Dinant La Merveilleuse The Grotte de Dinant La Merveilleuse is said to be one of the most beautiful caves in Belgium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General tips for Sweden</title>
      <link>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/general-tips-for-sweden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 10:46:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peppers-pawprint.com/en/general-tips-for-sweden/</guid>
      <description>It has always been my dream to live in Sweden for a while and this dream came true for my master’s degree. Pepper and I spent a total of 1.5 years in Sweden.
Travel I can only talk about my experiences to travel to Sweden from Germany:
 You can drive through Denmark and then use the Öresund bridge between Copenhagen and Malmö. This bridge connects the two countries. It is easy to buy the tickets online so you don&#39;t have to queue in front of the bridge.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>